Review exercise 513 speed reading. Repeat the paragraph from review exercise 155 as
quickly as possible.
Think the United Auto Workers can beat Caterpillar Incorporated in their bitter
contract battle? Before placing your beds talk to Paul Brannon, who can't wait to
cross the picket line at Caterpillar's factory in East Peoria. Brannon, recently
laid off by a rubber parts plant, where he earned base pay of $6.30 an hour, lives
one block from a heavily picketed gate at the cat complex. Now he's applying to
replace one of 12,600 workers who've been on strike for the past five months. $17 an
hour and they don't want to work? asked Brannon. I don't want to take another
guy's job, but I'm hurting too.